Guide to the Eastern Connecticut State University Events Collection 1891-2010 MS 0xx
Eastern Connecticut State University, Publisher
- Series XIV - Special Events
  - Honoring Dr. Carter, Spring 2006 (Box 3, Item 116)
  - Press Conference Introducing Dr. Nuñez, May 18, 2006 (Box 3, Item 117)
  - The Constitution: To Be or Not to Be?, Sep 21, 2006 (Box 3, Item 118)
  - ECSU Authors’ Event, Oct 26, 2006 (Box 3, Item 119)
  - Mostly Salzburg, 2007 (Box 3, Item 120)
  - “The Witching Hour” an history symposium, Nov 7, 2009 (Box 3, Item 121)
- Series XV - Special Guests
  - Lionel Hampton, 1984 (Box 3, Item 122)
  - Lily Yuan, Mar 1, 1988 (Box 3, Item 123)
  - Shirley Chisholm, [1992] (Box 3, Item 124)
  - Jackie Pflug- A Time for Reflection, 2001 (Box 3, Item 125)
  - Suarez, Apr 20, 2004 (Box 3, Item 126)
  - Alyx Kellington, Sep 1, 2004 (Box 3, Item 127)
  - Robert J.S. Ross, 2005 (Box 3, Item 128)
  - Reyna Grande, Sep 26, 2007 (Box 3, Item 129)
  - Julia Muench, Apr 8, 2009 (Box 3, Item 130)
- Series XVI - University Hour
  - University Hour Spring 1997 (Box 3, Item 131)
  - University Hour Fall 1997 (Box 3, Item 132)
  - University Hour Spring 1998 (Box 3, Item 133)
  - University Hour Fall 1998 (Box 3, Item 134)
  - University Hour Spring 1999 (Box 3, Item 135)
  - University Hour Fall 1999 (Box 3, Item 136)
  - University Hour Spring 2000 (Box 3, Item 137)
  - University Hour Fall 2000 (Box 3, Item 138)
  - University Hour Spring 2001 (Box 3, Item 139)
  - University Hour Fall 2001 (Box 3, Item 140)
  - University Hour Spring 2002 (Box 3, Item 141)
  - University Hour Fall 2002 (Box 3, Item 142)
  - University Hour Spring 2003 (Box 3, Item 143)
  - University Hour Fall 2003 (Box 3, Item 144)
  - University Hour Spring 2004 (Box 3, Item 145)
  - University Hour Fall 2004 (Box 3, Item 146)
  - University Hour Spring 2005 (Box 3, Item 147)
  - University Hour 2005-2006 (Box 3, Item 148)
  - University Hour Fall 2005/Spring 2006, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Item 149)
  - University Hour Fall 2006 (Box 3, Item 150)